{
    "subject": "resource/Claudio_Bieler",
    "predicate": "property/clubs",
    "object": "resource/Racing_Club_de_Avellaneda",
    "human_readable": "Claudio Bieler played for Racing Club de Avellaneda.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9879968762397766,
            "question": "Was Claudio Bieler associated with Racing Club de Avellaneda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9462884068489075,
            "question": "Who played for Racing Club de Avellaneda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8334470391273499,
            "question": "What is the name of the club Claudio Bieler played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8201607465744019,
            "question": "Can you name a club Claudio Bieler played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8170497417449951,
            "question": "What is the full name of the club Claudio Bieler played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8016822338104248,
            "question": "For which football club did Claudio Bieler play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7766116261482239,
            "question": "Is Racing Club de Avellaneda a football club?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6205875873565674,
            "question": "What sport did Claudio Bieler play professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.539399266242981,
            "question": "Where did Claudio Bieler play football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49059268832206726,
            "question": "Is Racing Club de Avellaneda located in Argentina?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Claudio Bieler played for Racing Club de Avellaneda.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2630_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Claudio Bieler play football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2630_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport did Claudio Bieler play professionally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2630_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Racing Club de Avellaneda a football club?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2630_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2630_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There are multiple documents mentioning Claudio Bieler, a professional football player from Argentina.\n* One of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2630/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt) mentions that Racing claimed the Copa Ciudad de Mar del Plata with a 2-1 win over their Avellaneda rivals, and Claudio Bieler scored a goal for Racing.\n* Another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2630/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt) mentions that on January 6, 2010, Racing Club de Avellaneda signed Claudio Bieler to a three-and-a half year contract.\n\nBased on this information, I conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Claudio Bieler played for Racing Club de Avellaneda. Specifically, it mentions his signing with Racing Club on January 6, 2010, for a three-and-a-half-year contract."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}